Guide to the Radio TV Reports Infomercial Collection, 1990-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Tapes, 1990-1996
  - Tape 113
    - The Joy of Juicing. WWOR-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 114
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthroughs II. WWOR-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 6:00 AM.
    - Edgar Morris--Your Face Is Your Passport. WWOR-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 6:30 AM.
    - St. Go of Beverly Hills Age Free Skin. WWOR-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 7:00 AM.
    - Nordic Track--The Fit One. WWOR-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 115
    - Hooked on Phonics. WPIX-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 6:30 AM.
    - Carlton Sheets Home Study Course. WPIX-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 116
    - Freedom from Pain--Therapy Plus. WPIX-TV. 1992 Mar. 14. 7:00 AM.
    - Bob Mann's Golf Dynamics vol. II. WPIX-TV. 1992 Mar. 14. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 117
    - Hooked on Phonics. WPIX-TV. 1992 Mar. 21. 6:30 AM.
    - Ronco Drain Buster, Door Saver and Food Dehydrator. WPIX-TV. 1992 Mar. 21. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 1118
    - Brain Supercharger--Millionaire's Mind. WNBC-TV. 1992 Mar. 21. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 119
    - Making of a Commercial. WPIX-TV. 1992 Apr. 11. 8:00 AM.
    - The Joy of Juicing. WPIX-TV. 1992 Apr. 11. 8:30 AM.
    - Superstep Stairclimber. WPIX-TV. 1992 Apr. 11. 9:00 AM.
    - Juice Tiger Machine--Jack LaLane. WPIX-TV. 1992 Apr. 11. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 120
    - Golfing Breakthrough for the 90s. WNYW-TV. 1992 Apr. 12. 11:00 AM.
    - Body Plus (American Gladiators). WNYW-TV. 1992 Apr. 12. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 121
    - Hooked on Phonics. WPIX-TV. 1992 May 9. 6:30 AM.
    - See and Hear Piano Series. WPIX-TV. 1992 May 9. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 122
    - Blu Blocker sunglasses. WPIX-TV. 1992 May 9. 8:00 AM.
    - Win the War Against Acne. WPIX-TV. 1992 May 9. 8:30 AM.
    - Colorcote 2000--Car Care Polish. WPIX-TV. 1992 May 9. 9:00 AM.
    - Superstep Stairclimber. WPIX-TV. 1992 May 9. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 123
    - Cher's Beauty Products. WNBC-TV. 1992 May 30. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 124
    - Whitney Leadership Group. WWOR-TV. 1992 May 31. 12:00 AM.
    - Nu/Hart Clinics. WWOR-TV. 1992 May 31. 12:30 AM.
    - Hair Club for Men. WWOR-TV. 1992 May 31. 1:00 AM.
    - Love Phone--Jessica Hahn. WWOR-TV. 1992 May 31. 1:30 AM.
  - Tape 125 (Box 5)
    - Getting Rich in America. WNYW-TV. 1992 May 26. 12:30 AM.
  - Tape 126
    - Nu/Hart Clinics. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 6:00 AM.
    - Be Your Own Boss. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 6:30AM.
    - Gripmaster. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 7:00 AM.
    - Stepsaver. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 127
    - Kathy Smith Diet--Fat Burning System. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 8:00 AM.
    - Acne Statin. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 8:30 AM.
    - Hair Club for Men. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 9:00 AM.
    - Fitness Quest--Skiing. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 128
    - Hooked on Phonics. WPIX-TV. 1992 June 20. 6:30 AM.
    - New Juice Man. WPIX-TV. 1992 June 20. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 129
    - Nu/Hart Clinics. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 20. 6:00 AM.
    - Be Your Own Boss. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 20. 6:30AM.
    - Invisions Hair Restoration. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 20. 7:00 AM.
    - Superstep Stairclimber. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 20. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 130
    - Deal a Meal. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 20. 10:00 AM.
    - Cher's Beauty Products. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 20. 10:30 AM.
    - Psychic Friends Network. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 20. 11:00 AM.
    - Victoria Jackson III. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 20. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 131
    - Deal a Meal. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 10:00 AM.
    - Victoria Jackson. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 10:30 AM.
    - Cher's Beauty Products. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 11:00 AM.
    - Big Green Clean Machine. WWOR-TV. 1992 June 13. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 132
    - Conair Emjoi Twin. WPIX-TV. 1992 July 25. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 133
    - Time Life--The War Years. WWOR-TV. 1992 July 12. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 134
    - Psychic Friends Network. WPIX-TV. 1992 Sept. 5. 6:30 AM.
    - Flying Lure. WPIX-TV. 1992 Sept. 5. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 135
    - Toastmaster Grillerie. WNBC-TV. 1992 Aug. 29. 12:30 PM.
    - Big Green Clean Machine. WNBC-TV. 1992 Aug. 29. 1:00 PM.
    - Dura Lube. WNBC-TV. 1992 Aug. 29. 1:30 PM.
  - Tape 136
    - Deal a Meal. WWOR-TV. 1992 Sept. 19. 8:00 AM.
    - Jet Steam Oven--American Harvest. WWOR-TV. 1992 Sept. 19. 8:30 AM.
    - Hair Club for Men. WWOR-TV. 1992 Sept. 19. 9:00 AM.
    - Charles J. Givens. WWOR-TV. 1992 Sept. 19. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 137
    - Carlton Sheets Home Study Course. WPIX-TV. 1992 Sept. 12. 8:00 AM.
    - Stair Climber Plus. WPIX-TV. 1992 Sept. 12. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 138
    - Time Life--Your Hit Parade with Steve Allen. WWOR-TV. 1992 Sept. 12. 6:00 AM.
    - Deal a Meal. WWOR-TV. 1992 Sept. 12. 6:30 AM.
    - Hooked on Phonics. WWOR-TV. 1992 Sept. 12. 7:00 AM.
    - Jane Fonda. WWOR-TV. 1992 Sept. 12. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 139
    - Ross Perot Talks About Jobs, Debt and the Washington Mess. WCBS. 1992 Oct. 6. 8:00 PM.
  - Tape 140
    - GTE. KCOP. 1992 Oct. 24. 10:00 AM.
  - Tape 141
    - GLH Formula No. 9. WPIX-TV. 1992 Oct. 24. 6:30 AM.
    - Big Green Clean Machine. WPIX-TV. 1992 Oct. 24. 7:00 AM.
    - Choose to Be Healthy. WPIX-TV. 1992 Oct. 24. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 142
    - Oxygen Cocktail. WWOR-TV. 1992 Oct. 24. 12:30 AM.
  - Tape 143
    - C&P Telephone--The Ringers. WBFF. 1992 Nov. 10. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 144
    - Zero Pain. TNN. 1992 Oct. 24. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 145
    - How to Succeed Without a Job. WPIX-TV. 1992 Oct. 17. 6:30 AM.
    - Firmflex. WPIX-TV. 1992 Oct. 17. 7:00 AM.
    - New Juice Man. WPIX-TV. 1992 Oct. 17. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 146
    - J. A. Alternatives. WWOR-TV. 1992 Oct. 25. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 147
    - Deal a Meal. WWOR-TV. 1992 Oct. 25. 8:00 AM.
    - Psychic Friends Network. WWOR-TV. 1992 Oct. 25. 8:30 AM.
    - Miracle Blade II. WWOR-TV. 1992 Oct. 25. 9:00 AM.
    - Dave del Dotto. WWOR-TV. 1992 Oct. 25. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 148-151
    - Quik Cook. WNYW-TV. 1992 Oct. 11. 11:00 AM.
    - Braun--A Winning Smile. WWOR-TV. 1992 Nov. 21. 9:00 AM.
    - Deni Turbo-Seal. WGBO-TV. 1991 Sept. 28. 7:30 AM.
    - Quick 'n Brite. WTVX. 1991 Sept. 22. 12:00 PM.
  - Tape 152
    - McDougal. WPIX-TV. 1992 Nov. 14. 7:30 AM.
    - Acne Statin. WWOR-TV. 1992 Nov. 20. 9:00 AM.
    - Cross Walk. WPIX-TV. 1992 Nov. 14. 8:00 AM.
    - Psychic Friends Network. WWOR-TV. 1992 Nov. 28. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 153
    - Radio Shack Memorex. WPIX-TV. 1992 Dec. 5. 8:00 AM.
    - Making Money. WWOR-TV. 1992 Dec. 5. 7:00 AM.
    - Braun Slimline. WWOR-TV. 1992 Dec. 5. 9:00 AM.
    - Regal Shop. WNBC-TV. 1992 Dec. 5. 1:30 PM.
  - Tape 154
    - Golfing Breakthrough for the 90s. WNBC-TV. 1992 Dec. 5. 2:30 PM.
    - Lifeline Gym. WNBC-TV. 1992 Dec. 5. 3:30 PM.
    - Quik and Easy Skin Care. WNYW-TV. 1992 Dec. 23. 1:00 PM.
    - Incredible Sweater Machine. WNBC-TV. 1992 Dec. 23. 2:00 PM.
  - Tape 155
    - Natural Trim. WWOR-TV. 1992 Dec. 26. 8:30 AM.
    - Redkin. WWOR-TV. 1992 Dec. 26. 9:00 AM.
    - Stop the Insanity. WWOR-TV. 1992 Dec. 26. 9:30 AM.
    - Phase Out the Smoke. WWOR-TV. 1992 Dec. 26. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 156
    - Lori Davis Hair. WWOR-TV. 1993 Jan. 2. 8:00 AM.
    - Fit 1 Exercise Machine. WWOR-TV. 1993 Jan. 9. 7:30 AM.
    - California Diet Plan. WWOR-TV. 1993 Jan. 9. 11:00 AM.
    - Edgar Morris Skin Care. WWOR-TV. 1993 Jan. 16. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 157
    - Lasting Kiss. WWOR-TV. 1993 Jan. 30. 2:30 AM.
    - VCR Voice Programme. WPIX-TV. 1993 Jan. 23. 7:00 AM.
    - J. A. Alternatives. WWOR-TV. 1993 Jan. 31. 8:00 AM.
    - Financial Fitness. WNYW-TV. 1993 Feb. 01. 1:00 PM.
  - Tape 158 (Box 6)
    - Rags to Riches. WWOR-TV. 1993 Feb. 7. 8:00 AM.
    - Wealth Building Workshop. WCBS. 1993 Feb. 14. 7:30 AM.
    - Jet Aire Hair Styling. WPIX-TV. 1993 Feb. 27. 8:30 AM.
    - Sterling Home Water Filter. WPIX-TV. 1993 Mar. 6. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 159
    - Redken PDTS. WWOR-TV. 1993 Mar. 13. 9:30 AM.
    - Butterfly Ladder. WNYW-TV. 1993 Mar. 14. 11:30 AM.
    - Charles J. Givens. WNYW-TV. 1993 Mar. 20. 3:00 PM.
    - I. Q. Unlimited Computer. WWOR-TV. 1993 Mar. 27. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 160
    - Time Life Program Buy. WWOR-TV. 1993 Mar. 6. 7:30 AM.
    - Fitness Quest Stand-Up Batter. WWOR-TV. 1993 Apr. 3. 7:30 AM.
    - Hidden Key to Loving. WWOR-TV. 1993 Apr. 3. 8:00 AM.
    - Autofon Polish. TNN. 1993 Apr. 9. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 161
    - Avon. KTVX. 1993 Feb. 14. 7:00 AM.
    - Ross Perot. WNBC-TV. 1993 Apr. 25. 7:00 PM.
    - Tony Little. WPIX-TV. 1993 Apr. 24. 8:30 AM.
    - Kountry Kickin'.WPIX-TV. 1993 May 8. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 162
    - Making Money Secrets. WWOR-TV. 1993 May 8. 7:00 AM.
    - Journey into the New. WWOR-TV. 1993 May 8. 9:00 AM.
    - Kurtain and Kraft Home. WPIX-TV. 1993 May 15. 7:00 AM.
    - United We Stand America. WNBC-TV. 1993 May 30. 8:00 PM.
  - Tape 163
    - Perfect Smile. WWOR-TV. 1993 June 5. 10:00 AM.
    - Psychic Friends Network. WWOR-TV. 1993 June 5. 11:00 AM.
    - Dale Carnegie. WPIX-TV. 1993 June 12. 7:00 AM.
    - Eez-Away Relief. WWOR-TV. 1993 June 5. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 164
    - Family Entertainment Network. No station. 1993 June 12. 7:30 AM.
    - Charles J. Givens. No station. 1993 June 12. 4:00 PM.
    - Super Charger. No station. 1993 June 27. 12:30 PM.
    - Soloflex. No station. 1993 July 12. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 165
    - McDonald's. BET. 1993 July 17. 7:30 PM.
    - Popeil Pasta Maker. CNBC. 1993 June 27. 5:30 AM.
    - Norelco Satinelle. WWOR-TV. 1993 July 24. 8:30 AM.
    - Marshall Fields. WGN. 1993 June 26. 6:30 AM.
  - Tape 166
    - Microcrisp Microwave Wrap. WCBS. 1993 Aug. 8. 12:00 PM.
    - Regina Easy Pro Carpet Cleaner. WPIX-TV. 1993 Aug. 7. 7:00 AM.
    - St. Joseph's Indian School. WPIX-TV. 1993 Aug. 7. 7:30 AM.
    - Home Business Opportunities. WWOR-TV. 1993 Aug. 7. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 167
    - Ask Mike Computer Tutor. WWOR-TV. 1993 Aug. 21. 7:00 AM.
    - Jet Steam Oven 3000T. WWOR-TV. 1993 Aug. 21. 7:30 AM.
    - Duralon. WPIX-TV. 1993 Aug. 28. 7:00 AM.
    - Rhino Records BillboardLifetime. 1993 Sept. 5. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 168
    - Realm Fragrances by Erox. WWOR-TV. 1993 Sept. 18. 1:30 AM.
    - Gravity Edge. WCBS. 1993 Sept. 12. 7:30 AM.
    - Jet Stream Oven.WCIV. 1993 Aug. 7. 12:00 PM.
    - Refractive Surgery. WCPO. 1993 Sept. 19. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 169
    - Nothin' but Nets. WWOR-TV. 1993 Sept. 28. 6:00 AM.
    - Philips CDI. WWOR-TV. 1993 Sept. 18. 9:00 AM.
    - Interactive Network. WGBO-TV. 1993 Sept. 26. 7:00 AM.
    - Autofon Polish. WGBO-TV. 1993 Sept. 26. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 170
    - Biogime Skin Care. WFLD. 1993 Oct. 3. 9:30 AM.
    - The World of Peter Rabbit. WWOR-TV. 1993 Sept. 25. 10:00 AM.
    - Psychic Friends Network. WNYW-TV. 1993 Sept. 26. 11:30 AM.
    - Mini Max. WPIX-TV. 1993 Oct. 9. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 171
    - Buns of Steel. WNYW-TV. 1993 Nov. 14. 11:00 AM.
    - Snackmaster Dehydrator. WWOR-TV. 1993 Nov. 13. 8:00 AM.
    - Stop the Insanity. WWOR-TV. 1993 Nov. 6. 7:30 AM.
    - Skewdriver Pro Kit. WWOR-TV. 1993 Oct. 9. 8:30 PM.
  - Tape 172
    - Wilton's Let's Decorate. WWOR-TV. 1993 Oct. 9. 10:00 AM.
    - St Go Forever Young. WWOR-TV. 1993 Oct. 16. 7:30 AM.
    - Personal Power Program. WWOR-TV. 1993 Oct. 16. 9:30 AM.
    - Soloflex. WNYW-TV. 1993 Dec. 7. 1:00 PM.
  - Tape 173
    - Marshall Fields. WGN. 1993 June 26. 6:30 AM.
    - Nordic Flex Gold exercise machine. WWOR-TV. 1993 Dec. 4. 8:00 AM.
    - Bissell Little Green. WWOR-TV. 1993 Dec. 11. 7:30AM.
    - Edgar Morris Skin Care. WWOR-TV. 1993 Dec. 12. 5:00 AM.
  - Tape 175
    - Fitness Breakthrough. Lifetime. 1994 Jan. 2. 8:29 AM.
    - Pro-Form Cross Trainer. WWOR-TV. 1994 Jan. 1. 8:00 AM.
    - Principal Secrets--Victoria Principal. WWOR-TV. 1994 Jan. 10. 10:30 AM.
    - Consumer Infoline. WWOR-TV. 1994 Jan. 8. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 176
    - Desert Beauty Time. WWOR-TV. 1994 Jan. 8. 9:00 AM.
    - Mega Memory Photographic Memory. WWOR-TV. 1994 Jan. 8. 8:30 AM.
    - Kellogg's Just Right. CBS. 1994 Jan. 11. 1:16 PM.
    - Psychic Friends Network. WPIX-TV. 1994 Jan. 15. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 177
    - Dual-Action Acne Regimen. Lifetime. 1994 Jan. 23. 3:00 AM.
    - Braun PDTS Oral B Plaque Remover. WWOR-TV. 1994 Jan. 22. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 178
    - Video Professor. WPIX-TV. 1994 Jan. 22. 7:00 AM.
    - Health Rider. WCBS. 1994 Jan. 29. 5:05 AM.
    - Fantom Vacuum. WWOR-TV. 1994 Feb. 5. 9:30 AM.
    - Alex Langer Flying Lure. Family Channel. 1994 Mar. 11. 3:00 AM.
  - Tape 179
    - L.I. Medical Associates. WWOR-TV. 1994 Jan. 29. 7:30 AM.
    - Sandals Resort.WCBS. 1994 Feb. 5. 1:30 AM.
    - Dura Lube. TNN. 1994 Feb. 5. 8:29 AM.
    - 60-Second Grill Express. WWOR-TV. 1994 Feb. 12. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 180
    - Royal Diamond Cookware. WWOR-TV. 1994 Feb. 19. 9:00 AM.
    - MDR Fitness Tabs. Lifetime. 1994 Feb. 23. 2:00 PM.
    - Driveway Detailer. Lifetime. 1994 Mar. 11. 3:00 AM.
    - The Home Right Painting. Family Channel. 1994 Mar. 11. 2:30 AM.
  - Tape 181
    - Barbie Classic Collection. Lifetime. 1994 Mar. 13. 8:00 AM.
    - Health Rider. Lifetime. 1994 Mar. 13. 1:00 AM.
    - Nu Hart Hair Product. Lifetime. 1994 Mar. 13. 3:00 AM.
    - Fidelity Investment. KCRA. 1994 May 15. 12:00 PM.
  - Tape 182
    - Texaco Clean System Gasoline. WNBC-TV. 1994 Mar. 19. 1:30 PM.
    - Power Walk Plus. WWOR-TV. 1994 Mar. 19. 9:00 AM.
    - Fiberspeed 2000 Golf Shafts. WWOR-TV. 1994 Mar. 19. 9:30 AM.
    - Best Little Whorehouse in Texas. WPIX-TV. 1994 Mar. 26. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 183
    - Smart Mop. WWOR-TV. 1994 Mar. 26. 7:00 AM.
    - American Lecture Series Library. WNYW-TV. 1994 Mar. 27. 11:00 AM.
    - Homeright Painting. WWOR-TV. 1994 Apr. 9. 7:30 AM.
    - The Wireless Wonder. WNBC-TV. 1994 Apr. 16. 5:00 AM.
  - Tape 184
    - The Wireless Wonder. WNBC-TV. 1994 Apr. 16. 5:00 AM.
    - Home Furnishings Company. WNBC-TV. 1994 Apr. 17. 6:05 AM.
    - Juiceman Juicer. Family Channel. 1994 Apr. 28. 4:00 AM.
    - Maxmusic Program. ETV. 1994 Apr. 28. 3:00 AM.
  - Tape 185
    - Medicus Pro. WWOR-TV. 1994 May 7. 7:00 AM.
    - Time Life Sounds of the 70s. VH1. 1994 May 13. 4:00 AM.
    - Earth Preservation. WTBS. 1994 May 8. 3:30 AM.
    - Power Driver Screwdriver. WTBS. 1994 May 8. 4:00 AM.
  - Tape 186
    - Health 2000. KNSD. 1994 Mar. 31. 9:00 PM.
    - Hoover Wet/Dry Vacuum. WGBO-TV. 1994 May 28. 9:30 AM.
    - Kohler PDTS. WEWS. 1994 June 28. 2:46 AM.
    - Fixodent Denture Adhesive. WVIT. 1994 July 9. 12:30 PM.
  - Tape 187
    - Acne Statin. VH1. 1994 May 5. 4:00 AM.
    - Jojo's Psychic Alliance. VH1. 1994 May 17. 4:00 AM.
    - Natural Trim. WPIX-TV. 1994 May 14. 7:00 AM.
    - Kurtain Kraft European. Lifetime. 1994 May 8. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 188
    - Health Rider. WNYW-TV. 1994 May 22. 11:30 AM.
    - Buns of Steel. WWOR-TV. 1994 May 28. 8:30 AM.
    - Pyromid Outdoor Cooking. Discovery. 1994 May 28. 3:30 AM.
    - Denise Austin's Tone Up. WWOR-TV. 1994 June 11. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 189 (Box 7)
    - E-Z Mop. WPIX-TV. 1994 June 4. 7:30 AM.
    - Slick 50 Automotive Lubricant. TNN. 1994 July 9. 8:00 AM.
    - Rio Hair. WCBS. 1994 July 9. 3:30 PM.
    - Nucelle. Lifetime. 1994 May 16. 5:00 AM.
  - Tape 190
    - X-1R Friction Eliminator. Comedy Central. 1994 May 2. 5:30 AM.
    - Secrets of Making Love. Comedy Central. 1994 May 2. 4:30 AM.
    - Bio Slim Weight Loss. Comedy Central. 1994 May 10. 5:30 AM.
    - Time Life Sounds of the 70s. Lifetime. 1994 May 16. 5:30 AM.
  - Tape 191
    - Desert Beauty Time. Lifetime. 1994 Feb. 27. 9:00 AM.
    - HBO Home Box Office. BET. 1994 June 18. 6:30 PM.
    - Murad Most Beautiful. WWOR-TV. 1994 July 2. 8:30 AM.
    - Roland Martin's Helicopter Lure. WWOR-TV. No date. No time.
  - Tape 192
    - Quick 'n Brite. WGBO-TV. 1994 Aug. 9. 6:00 AM.
    - Kohler PDTS. KTVI. 1994 June 28. 2:40 PM.
    - Alien Golf Club. WBBM. 1994 Aug. 28. 12:00 PM.
    - Life Fitness Exerciser. Comedy Central. 1994 July 20. 5:00 AM.
  - Tape 193
    - Passion Profit and Power. WWOR-TV. 1994 June 18. 9:30 AM.
    - Hip and Thigh Machine. USA. 1994 Mar. 14. 3:30 AM.
    - Super Slicer. Comedy Central. 1994 July 20. 4:30 AM.
    - Memory Power Home Study. WNBC-TV. 1994 July 25. 2:38 AM.
  - Tape 194
    - Alien Golf Club. WPIX-TV. 1994 Sept. 3. 8:30 AM.
    - Perfect Smile. WWOR-TV. 1994 Sept. 3. 10:30 AM.
    - Remington's Soundmate. WWOR-TV. 1994 Sept. 10. 10:00 AM.
    - Microbuddy Microwave. WCBS. 1994 Sept. 24. 2:30 PM.
  - Tape 195
    - Tony Little Ab Isolator. WWOR-TV. 1994 Oct. 8. 11:00 AM.
    - Inteliquest. CNBC. 1994 Oct. 4. 3:30 AM.
    - American Business. WCBS. 1994 Oct. 8. 1:30 PM.
    - HBO Home Box Office. BET. 1994 June 18. 6:30 PM.
  - Tape 196
    - Toyota Motor Sales. WCBS. 1994 Nov. 5. 2:00 PM.
    - Tops Appliance City. WPIX-TV. 1994 Nov. 4. 12:20 AM.
    - Magnavox PDTS. WWOR-TV. 1994 Nov. 5. 8:30 AM.
    - Body by Jake Ab and Back.WWOR-TV. 1994 Nov. 5. 10:00 AM.
  - Tape 197
    - Hidden Keys. WPIX-TV. 1994 July 30. 8:00 AM.
    - Vitapower. Comedy Central. 1994 Sept. 1. 5:00 AM.
    - Fisher Appliances. WCBS. 1994 Oct. 30. 2:00 PM.
    - The Clinton Chronicles. WWOR-TV. 1994 Oct. 29. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 198
    - Perfect Hair System. WCBS. 1994 Nov. 12. 2:00 PM.
    - Bissell Plus Vacuum. WWOR-TV. 1994 Nov. 26. 10:00 AM.
    - Power Foam Carpet Cleaner. WNBC-TV. 1994 Nov. 22. 3:06 AM.
    - Better Blocks. Discovery. 1994 Nov. 14. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 199
    - Tone Up 1 2 3. Lifetime. 1994 Dec. 1. 2:30 PM.
    - Luxurious Hair Extensions. Lifetime. 1994 Dec. 1. 4:30 PM.
    - Apple PDTS Computer. WABC. 1994 Dec. 2. 5:30 AM.
    - The Nativity Cross. WWOR-TV. 1994 Dec. 3. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 200
    - Fortunoff the Source. WPIX-TV. 1994 Nov. 26. 8:30 AM.
    - Bissell Plus Vacuum. WWOR-TV. 1994 Nov. 26. 10:00 AM.
    - Sega CD. WCBS. 1994 Nov. 25. 2:05 AM.
    - Nowet Wonder Foam Cleaner. WWOR-TV. 1994 Dec. 24. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 201
    - Purina Pet Dry Dog Food. WNYW-TV. 1994 Nov. 4. 10:38 AM.
    - Secret Hair Program. Lifetime. 1994 Aug. 31. 3:30 AM.
    - Target Discount Program. WPWR. 1994 Nov. 26. 9:00 AM.
    - Geo Safari. WWOR-TV. 1995 Jan. 7. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 202
    - Bosley Medical Institute. NBC. 1995 Jan. 22. 1:32 PM.
    - Travel Perks. WWOR-TV. 1995 Jan. 21. 10:30 AM.
    - Quick 'n Brite. WWOR-TV. 1995 Jan. 21. 11:30 AM.
    - National Home Business. WPIX-TV. 1995 Jan. 21. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 203
    - Berland's House of Tools. WGBO-TV. 1994 Nov. 26. 8:30 AM.
    - Chevrolet Trucks. WBBM. 1994 Nov. 26. 5:10 AM.
    - Tony Little Videos. WLS. 1994 June 18. 10:00 AM.
    - U.S. Healthcare Medical Insurance. CBS. 1994 Nov. 26. 1:00 PM.
  - Tape 204
    - Power Driver Screwdriver. TNN. 1995 Jan. 1. 8:00 AM.
    - Financial Freedom. WNBC-TV. 1995 Jan. 9. 2:37 AM.
    - Braun PDTS Hand Blender. WWOR-TV. 1995 Jan. 7. 9:30 AM.
    - Fast Track Exerciser. WWOR-TV. 1994 Nov. 26. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 205
    - Braun PDTS Oral B Plaque Remover. WWOR-TV. 1995 Jan. 28. 9:30 AM.
    - National Strategic Alliance. WPIX-TV. 1995 Jan. 28. 7:30 AM.
    - Money Makers Live Program. WNBC-TV. 1995 Jan. 28. 5:00 AM.
    - Circuit City. WLS. 1995 Jan. 29. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 206
    - New Hair Institute. WNBC-TV. 1995 Feb. 4. 3:30 AM.
    - Pasta Express. WABC. 1995 Feb. 4. 4:00 AM.
    - Bread Classic 2000. WCBS. 1995 Feb. 4. 5:30 AM.
    - E-Force. WWOR-TV. 1995 Feb. 4. 9:00 AM.
  - Tape 207
    - Kitchen Wizard. WNBC-TV. 1995 Feb. 20. 3:06 AM.
    - Dual-Action Acne Regimen. WWOR-TV. 1995 Feb. 11. 7:30 AM.
    - Abflex Exerciser. WWOR-TV. 1995 Feb. 18. 8:30 AM.
    - T Touch Pet Training. WABC. 1995 Feb. 25. 4:00 AM.
  - Tape 208
    - Charles J. Givens. WPIX-TV. 1995 Mar. 4. 7:30 AM.
    - Roly Kit Organizer. WPIX-TV. 1995 Mar. 4. 8:30 AM.
    - Smart Chopper. WWOR-TV. 1995 Mar. 4. 10:30 AM.
    - Sonicare Toothbrush. CNBC. 1995 Mar. 5. 3:00 PM.
  - Tape 209
    - Dance Mix USA '95. WNBC-TV. 1995 Mar. 7. 3:06 AM.
    - Touchless Instant Restoration. WWOR-TV. 1995 Feb. 25. 7:00 AM.
    - Walkfit. WWOR-TV. 1995 Feb. 25. 10:30 AM.
    - Farewell to Fat. WWOR-TV. 1995 Feb. 25. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 210
    - Realm Fragrances Men's and Women's. Sci-Fi. 1995 Mar. 22. 3:30 AM.
    - Face-Fit Facial Exerciser. Sci-Fi. 1995 Mar. 22. 4:30 AM.
    - Third Federal Savings and Loan. WEWS. 1995 Feb. 12. 1:00 PM.
    - Principal Secrets--Victoria Principal. Comedy Central. 1995 Jan. 23. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 211
    - Powertrainer Exercise Machine. Comedy Central. 1995 Mar. 20. 7:00 AM.
    - The Wholesale Buying Guide. Lifetime. 1995 Mar. 21. 7:00 AM.
    - Better Blocks. WTTE. 1994 Dec. 21. 11:19 PM.
    - Bosley Medical Institute. USA. 1995 Jan. 22. 4:30 AM.
  - Tape 212
    - Attacking Anxiety II. WWOR-TV. 1995 Apr. 1. 8:00 AM.
    - Ez-Chopper. WWOR-TV. 1995 Apr. 8. 11:30 AM.
    - Time Life Dick Clark. ETV. 1995 Mar. 23. 3:30 AM.
    - Sony PDTS Minidisc. CNBC. 1995 Apr. 2. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 213
    - Where There Is a Will There Is an A--John Ritter. Lifetime. 1995 Mar. 22. 7:00 AM.
    - Infomercial Making. CBS. 1995 Apr. 8. 2:58 PM.
    - K-Tel 101 Greatest.Comedy Central. 1995 Apr. 20. 5:30 AM.
    - Five Attractions. WPIX-TV. 1994 June 18. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 214
    - Lesko's Info. WABC. 1995 Apr. 30. 6:00 AM.
    - Sophist-O-Twist Hair. WWOR-TV. 1995 Apr. 29. 9:30 AM.
    - San Antonio Promotion. Lifetime. 1995 Apr. 25. 7:00 AM.
    - Health Rider. WWOR-TV. 1995 May 6. 10:00 AM.
  - Tape 215
    - Mathemagics. WCBS. 1995 May 27. 2:00 PM.
    - Psychic Friends Network. WWOR-TV. 1995 May 20. 7:00 AM.
    - Five Attractions. WPIX-TV. 1994 June 18. 8:30 AM.
    - Autobike Classic. TNN. 1995 May 28. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 216
    - Feed the Children. WNBC-TV. 1995 May 10. 2:38 AM.
    - Home Right Painting. WWOR-TV. 1995 May 13. 9:30 AM.
    - Nature Sleep Mattress. CNBC. 1995 May 11. 3:30 AM.
    - Champions of Entrepreneurs. WNBC-TV. 1995 May 8. 2:38 AM.
  - Tape 217
    - Pedigree Pet Foods. CNBC. 1995 June 23. 4:00 PM.
    - Victoria Jackson. WNBC-TV. 1995 June 3. 1:30 PM.
    - Golfsmith Golf Club. CNBC. 1995 May 20. 2:00 PM.
    - Making Life Easier. WWOR-TV. 1995 June 10. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 218
    - Durashine Advanced Auto Polish. WNBC-TV. 1995 May 20. 3:30 AM.
    - AT&T. WCIX. 1995 June 25. 11:30 AM.
    - Tempo Trainer 911. SPCH. 1995 June 7. 9:30 AM.
    - Playboy Magazine. Comedy Central. 1995 June 19. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 219 (Box 8)
    - The Compact Chair. WWOR-TV. 1995 June 17. 10:30 AM.
    - Eagle Eyes. WWOR-TV. 1995 June 17. 8:00 AM.
    - Magnavox CD-1 System. WNYW-TV. 1995 June 18. 11:30 AM.
    - Sears Kenmore Hepa. Lifetime. 1995 June 20. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 220
    - Rogaine Hair Treatment. Lifetime. 1995 June 28. 7:00 AM.
    - Home Business Network. WPIX-TV. 1995 June 24. 8:30 AM.
    - Lexus Certified Pre-Owned Automobiles. WABC. 1995 July 8. 1:00 PM.
    - Food Dehydrator. KASN. 1995 July 3. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 221
    - Hy G Ionic Toothbrush. TNN. 1995 July 15. 8:00 AM.
    - Mathemagics. BET. 1995 July 15. 11:00 PM.
    - Chrysler Plymouth Dealers. WPIX-TV. 1995 July 15. 6:15 PM.
    - AT&T. WNYW-TV. 1995 July 16. 11:00 AM.
  - Tape 222
    - American Business. WPIX-TV. 1995 Aug. 5. 6:00 AM.
    - Natural Cover Make-Up. TVFN. 1995 Aug. 16. 5:30 AM.
    - Remembering the 80s. WWOR-TV. 1995 Aug. 20. 1:00 AM.
    - Aspen Wellness Group. WCBS. 1995 Aug. 19. 2:00 PM.
  - Tape 223
    - Pedigree Pet Foods. CNBC. 1995 Apr. 23. 4:00PM.
    - Bosley Medical Institute. NBC. 1995 Aug. 24. 2:42 AM.
    - Stilson & Stilson. NBC. 1995 Aug. 24. 8:11 AM.
    - RCA Digital Satellite. WPIX-TV. 1995 Aug. 26. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 224
    - Microsoft Windows. WNBC-TV. 1995 Aug. 27. 3:30 PM.
    - Sweepa Rubber Broom. WWOR-TV. 1995 Sept. 30. 10:30 AM.
    - Thermoscan. WABC. 1995 Oct. 20. 4:00 AM.
    - Lightolier. WWOR-TV. 1995 Oct. 21. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 225
    - Cholestaway Dietary Supplement. Discovery. 1995 Sept. 23. 8:00 AM.
    - Command Performance. WNBC-TV. 1995 Oct. 9. 2:37 AM.
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1995 Sept. 30. 7:30 AM.
    - Sweepa Rubber Broom. WWOR-TV. 1995 Sept. 30. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 226
    - Proactiv Solution. Lifetime. 1995 Sept. 18. 2:00 AM.